I've made millions of dollars in crypto
and crypto's the only place where you
can go verify this on chain yourself.
I've been documenting it on this YouTube
channel for the last 2 years and this
year I've sat across the table with a
few guys and interviewed a guy who made
2.5 mil in 33 minutes, another guy who
made 5.4 mil a year trading meme coins.
And the thing is that like you know, all
these guys didn't start with real money.
You know, a lot of these guys started
with just a few hundred bucks and
honestly trading has become easier than
ever. I mean, [music] 2 years ago some
of the tutorials I was making were like
literal trenching, like how to actually
like read on chain and all this stuff,
stuff that you don't really need to
understand like entirely anymore. Like
right now, I think it's really easy.
Literally 2 days ago there was a trader
who turned $30 into over $100,000. This
guy is Samisa_BTC.
We can follow him here on Fomo and you
guys can see the P&L yourself right
here. Share, boom. 30 bucks and he's
actually I think is he still holding
this?
Wow.
Yeah, look, he bought $30 at a $3,000
market cap July 13th at 4:43 p.m. and
now yeah, he's up $94,000 on this $30
position right now. And like this is the
real trade that this guy actually took.
Right? And I think like again, now more
than ever it's like all so like public
out there and you can really see what
everyone is doing. This guy Samisa
again, I don't even really know who this
guy is. I just followed him on on CT and
you guys know like crypto Twitter's
always been at like the heart of meme
coins. Like being on Twitter and
understanding [music] like who everyone
is has always been such a key part
of trading. But like this is the real
trade and there's been so many crazy
examples recently. Look, this guy right
here, Chippy Hodlner. He turned 70 bucks
into over 100 grand, but I think he
round tripped a lot of it. And yeah,
it's this position right here. Look,
$70,000 into $10,000. Wait, what?
Thought it was Oh, sorry. Uh 25 grand
and now he's up uh 10k. But still, I
mean, that's nuts from 70 bucks. And
trades like this are happening every
single day.
And
I mean, let's just get right into it,
right? Like, what what do meme coins
look like nowadays? You know, I spent
many, many, many, many my I spent way
too much time like just being here
looking at new pairs 24/7. And it got to
a point where like eventually I got
burnt out myself. Like I I was I was
trying so hard to be on top of the meme
coin game, but it it just got so like
time overwhelming. And I as I realized
like so many of like the greatest
traders like aren't doing this. Like,
they're not staring at the new pairs
24/7. You know, we sat down, like I
said, with Incentives earlier this year,
who's honestly like one of the best
traders. And just recently he was up
super fat on a position where he made
$330,000 on Cash Cat. And I believe he
ended up round tripping a lot of this.
But
in the last few weeks we have had so
many different like meme coin
opportunities. We had Anthem like come
out of nowhere and go to like 400
million more dollar market cap. And I I
played this trade terribly. I mean, I'm
actually in it right now. I'm down
$3,000. But there's been so many people
who like absolutely cooked on this play.
I mean, I believe TJR uh was in this
trade. I don't even follow him on FOMO.
Oops, my bad. Uh he was in this trade.
He made $43,000 from it. And I believe
he was up actually a lot more um on this
trade. I know Brez was also in this
trade. Like, a lot of like just money
guys are in this trade. He's up $30,000
on it. I believe he round tripped uh a
bit too unless this isn't counting like
how much he's um already sold. Maybe
maybe it's not doing so. Um look
meme coins have its up and downs. Like,
there's going to be tons of times where,
you know, volume isn't hot. There's not
like a lot of tokens graduating. There's
not a lot of like tokens to buy really.
But
I recently gotten back into it myself. I
mean, I just built a $45,000 position in
Tung Tung Tung So for meme coin. Like, I
got $50,000 in here. These are some of
my trades recently. As you can see it's
been like nothing too too crazy, but you
know, I'm making a few hundred bucks
there, a few thousand bucks there. You
know, like I'm still actively trying to
do this. My biggest trade this year so
far was Multibook, which was a a base
like AI agentic narrative coin. And I
ended up making $86,000 on this. I
invested $71,000. I got a 2x on my
money. I also made $6,000 on Asteroid,
5K on Cup C, 5K on Mayweather, 4K on
Asteroid. Uh this one right here was
actually one of my bigger percentage
P&Ls recently. I turned 250 bucks into
2,300 bucks. And this all happened
within the span of a few minutes, I
believe. So at 5:52, I bought $250. And
just a little less than an hour um after
I had already 10x my money. So turning
250 bucks into 2,500 in under an hour.
And yeah, look, I mean these P&Ls aren't
super crazy. I'm not telling you that
like, you know, I am like this super
active meme coin goat. But I mean, the
thing is you can follow these guys who
are. Right? Like look at the last 24
hours. Juicy is up $166,000.
And I think yeah, a lot of this is on 10
days, which is a Robinhood meme coin
narrative. So the CEO of Robinhood,
Vlad, has been tweeting a lot about uh
memes because Robinhood uh just
created their own a blockchain. So
they're trying to get like more activity
on this chain. And as you can see right
here, Vlad's been tweeting out out about
like memes and RWAs. These are like the
two main things that is happening on
Robinhood. And then Anthem and everyone
from CT, crypto Twitter, that's what CT
stands for, is uh interacting with Vlad
and making it go crazy. I believe Adam
here has some of the statistics of
Robinhood and the uh the trenches. So as
you can see right here,
total volume on the Robinhood chain. Uh
he just did tweet that it's been cooling
off over last few days. Um I I do
believe this is because like a lot of
people were expecting Vlad to interact
with Cash Cat. And so maybe I'm losing
you a little bit here. I'm going to take
a step back, okay? Meme coins
fundamentally is just an attention game.
Like, you're literally putting your
money on
betting if something's going to get more
attention than it's not. And a perfect
example of this is this like little
raccoon that's been going around. Like,
maybe you saw Jimothy. Dude,
this has to be one of the craziest
things ever, right? And so many
different FOMO theses have been like
shown upon this, right? If we look at
this chart right here, I'm sure we're
going to see theses going all the way
up. So, on FOMO, like each of these
little bubbles is like uh notification
of thesis uh of why some people think
the coin's going to go up. So, as you
can see right here, this guy, Sheep, had
the first thesis on this coin, and he
has turned $61 into 5,800. So, he
actually got rewarded for being
extremely early, and he was the first
thesis on this coin, Jimothy. But,
anyways, I don't know too much about
this myself. This seems to be like some
raccoon that is like has like a little
bit of a disability, and it's been going
extremely viral. It's been getting
talked upon. But, the one guy who I did
see talk about this was Jack Du Vall,
who's like someone who's really known
inside of like like our little meme
ecosystem, and he's been non-stop
talking about Jimothy. And the
interesting thing here is is that this
is a, you know, this coin literally came
out yesterday. It This animal has been
going so viral. And like, if you think
back, maybe you were already in meme
coins with me last year or something,
but like we've had very similar
situations with like Moodang, with
Peanut the Squirrel. I mean, Peanut the
Squirrel was a meme coin that ended up
going to $2 billion in market cap.
People literally made tens of millions
of dollars across these coins. Like,
there's some serious money here. So,
when something like Jimothy happens, you
know, when a coin that's 2 days old
touches $23 million in market cap, goes
15 mil.
And And guys, I mean, as someone who's
holding a crap ton of Tung Tung Tung So
Fur Coin, TTT, that's probably one of
the biggest like meme coins of all time.
This coin itself has only peaked at 23
mil, right? And this coin has been out
for months, I believe. And I just
recently started gathering a position on
it, but this coin's been out since
March, you know? And like people have
been running thesis all the way since
back here, and it really is one of the
most viral memes of our generation, but
Jimothy, this raccoon who came out in
one day, is just completely surpassing
the chart, and you have to ask yourself,
"Okay, why?"
Right? And it's because it's getting a
lot of attention right now. And you
always have to understand this, right?
Like meme coins, fundamentally, yeah,
they they are pump and dump. Like this
coin
if Jimothy doesn't continue going viral,
it'll go down, you know? And that's like
where you have to decide. No, I think
like there's certain memes that are kind
of here forever. That's why I got in a
position in Triple T. Um
but, you know, you kind of just have to
like decide like what what it is that
you you want to do. And as a trader, you
want to be trading everything everything
that's viral. So, I should have
definitely gotten myself involved into
Jimothy. I mean, I follow so many people
um
on FOMO. I got so many of these
notifications. Rold is a great trader,
too. I follow him. Zink, like I saw
Zink's, you know, thesis when he put
this. And
yeah, I just did I decided not to buy.
But, a meme coin is fundamentally just
attention with like some ticker and some
price attached next to it. There's no
product, you know, I mean, there can be,
you know, like a lot of like the memes
and the coins that people trade on chain
can be products, can be revenue, stuff
like that. But, I think like
fundamentally, a lot of stuff that goes
up super quickly is just like funny meme
coins. Like you know, nothing you really
have to do research on, but, you know,
it's always important to know how to do
research. Like if you want to go ahead
here, go to go on Jimothy, and then go
ahead and look on chain, go on
Dexscreener, type in the contract
address, and then you can look at like
all the extra details if you would like
to, you know, like all the KOLs, because
not everybody is on FOMO. FOMO just
shows like all the holders who are
buying and trading this coin on FOMO,
but there's a lot of different trading
platforms out there. So, something like
Dexscreener kind of shows you that
across everything. Shows you all the
KOLs who have been top traders, who are
currently holders.
So, like right here, Cooker, who's
somebody we interviewed on this channel
as well, looks like he made $21,000, and
you can click his profile directly from
here and go ahead and follow him if you
like.
Um you can check like across all the
holders who they are. You can check the
bubble maps. All this stuff is like
really good to know how to do.
But I kind of want this video to stick
to the more fundamental one and just
like going over the basics. If you guys
want me to go like over how to read on
chain and all that stuff, I I can do so
in a in a later video, but I think right
now I kind of just want to give you guys
a refresh of like okay, like what is
meme coins? What's a super beginner
guide? How do I get started right now?
And I literally just did this. I created
this brand new FOMO account like
literally super easy. Go into the link
in the description right now. Sign up
right here and you're going to get an
account. You're going to get money.
Deposit Solana USDC. Super simple. So I
put 100 bucks here.
And then, you know, I can go to the
leaderboard here 24 hours, 7 days, 30
days, and all time. And for example,
change is the all time P&L leader on
here. I can follow him. Frank's made a
million dollars on FOMO. I can follow
him. Logjam's made 900k. I can follow
them. And now that I follow them, I have
notifications on for them. And whenever
something I'll get a notification on my
phone. FOMO makes it like really easy to
trade on on your phone or whatnot. Um
Logjam right here, look at him. He's got
$223,000 position in a toom toom toom
for work coin.
So
and that's bullish for me. He's been uh
sending some tokens out. I wonder if
he's been selling.
Um
but yeah, you know, I I follow these
guys and then I go here on the feed. I
have this open. See what's like actively
going on in the trenches. And it's just
worth having this open, right? Because
like when something big happens and when
I mean big, something like CashApp for
example, or something like yesterday we
had uh Brian, the CEO of Coinbase,
change his profile picture. I'm going to
uh show you this.
Brian Armstrong, he's the CEO of
Coinbase, uh which has the base chain.
He changed his profile picture to this.
And as soon as he did that, you know,
the feed was going crazy and there was
this token called Brian, Coinbase man,
that ended up going to like $20 million
in market cap. So, look at this. They
went to 33 mil, unless that's a med
wick, I believe it is. Um could be
wrong. Let me turn off the thesis here.
So, yeah, went actually 30 mil, which is
insane. And as you can see here, this
candle right here was sitting above, you
know, around the hundreds of K's. It
went all the way up to 18 million just a
few minutes. For 15 mil, and then it
went back up to 30 mil. Like uh but
then, you know,
this is like an attention-based coin.
Brian obviously didn't continue talking
about this.
Uh I don't mean anything. The intention
was to like pump the coin. Maybe it was.
I don't know. They were trying to get
some attention on base, maybe. I don't
know. I'm not sure.
Um but when Brian changed his profile
picture back, as you can see, it's not
this CryptoPunk, this coin completely
dumped.
And so, why I'm telling you this is
because, you know, when this was
happening, I was getting notifications
on my phone nonstop like all these
traders are buying are buying Brian. And
I go look at the feed, and it's like a
lot of rotations going on. When a lot of
like when a specific narrative is
happening inside of our like crazy meme
coin ecosystem, people are going to sell
some positions. You know, because I
might do it, too. Like if Elon Musk
right now tweeted a funny dog or
something, maybe I go ahead and sell
some triple T uh because a lot of my
liquidity is tied up on it. Like as you
can see, I only have $2,000 here, but I
have 50,000 in my FOMO profile.
I might go ahead and sell some triple T,
like, you know, not permanently, but
just temporarily, so that I can I get
access to some liquidity to go ahead and
trade these new events. And when that
happens, and you see on the feed
everyone is selling, like right now,
Vayn just sold Jimothy or whatever. If
you see these rotations happening, it
kind of gives you some entries into some
of these better, more long-term coins.
Um
So, yeah, I have 100 loaded up into this
brand new account. You know, I'm I'm
seeing Logjam has this crazy P&L. He's
in NEET. You know, if I want to go ahead
and buy $5 of NEET just because, you
know, this top trader on FOMO did that
same thing. You know, triple T, buy $5
of that, whatever.
Um or just memes that maybe you see,
right? I think the best way to do this
yourself and like actually trade
yourself is just like when you're
scrolling on TikTok, Instagram, social
media, when you're going day-to-day
life, when you're seeing things that you
think are you're early to and they might
go more viral.
Whether that be like a freaking Labubu
for example. Like I remember months ago
Labubus were like a crazy trend and this
is not the official Labubu coin by the
way. This is a scam. I'm not sure why uh
Look at right here. It says warning
potential scam. If you ever see this on
FOMO, please pay attention. Um yeah,
100% this coin is a scam. Uh but there
was a real Labubu uh token and I'm not
sure why it's not showing up right now.
Let me see here. Tokens. That's actually
really weird. Uh on Dex. Even if I look
it up though, I should be able to find
it. Yeah, I will I do believe it's this
one. Uh copy it. Boom.
Uh control A. Paste that CA. Boom. So
like Labubu obviously now it's a dead
trend, but like man, this was going
absolutely crazy. Like look how high
this pumped. Went to 75 million and I
don't think Yeah, people weren't trading
on FOMO
um
back then.
But I'm just saying like, you know, if
you were early to Labubu, I mean, you
had Oh my gosh, you had like months to
buy Labubu really. And even right here
in May when it first went up to 10 mil,
it kind of like was dying out and then
bro, like it really just went all the
way up. So Yeah, this is how you have to
play meme coins, right? Like, you know,
LeBron right now he's deciding what team
he's going to go to. If LeBron goes to
the Miami Heat for example, I don't
know. I don't I I I've no idea what I'm
saying. But if there was some like
sort of coin or something that I thought
would go more viral as time goes, like
that's an example of something I would
buy. Okay? Next, okay? Right now we have
the feed open. We have these tokens tab
right here. All the tokens that are
graduating, the ones that are bonding,
that they're about to bond, you know, I
can click on all these tokens and kind
of check them out. So like ASMR, I'm
just doing like some live scanning right
now like what I would really do.
So like let's say ASMR coin here. I want
to buy this raccoon, right? So I'm going
to go ahead and buy I'm going to like
actually buy $50 worth of this raccoon.
Remember, I just made this profile right
now. So like no one has this.
Um I'm just like doing this live trade
right now. All right. So
I'm in this trade
on that brand new FOMO profile I made.
I'm doing like actual research right
now.
I'm going to go ahead and copy the CA.
I'm going to go ahead and here Deck
Screener, put the CA in.
Look at some of the holders and maybe
some KO wallets are in.
You know, see who has these on FOMO if
there's any thesis here.
Let me go over to the Twitter community.
Bio raccoon gets caught smoking meth.
Um
going to 1 million 2 funny. So, this
like right now I'm looking like this was
almost a year ago, a year and 2 months
ago. So, like I don't think the meme is
too too too crazy, but the reason that
they're trying to like bond this coin
and send it is because of uh the Jimothy
coin that I was talking about earlier.
So, right now I am actually up $3 on
this trade and I think I'm going to
actually sell. I don't know how much
I'll sell for.
So, I actually ended up making $2 on
this trade. So, first ever trade and I
found this token by going here to
bonding. You know, bonding is all the
tokens that are about to graduate and
it's just like these are like the newer
tokens that people are trying to
graduate and then over here in the
graduate section is a
tokens that are highly volatile. Tokens
can be launched by anyone including bad
actors. They have those little warnings
which are just important to know. Um but
obviously like when you are trading and
stuff like just just remember those
things. Uh so, tokens have bonding open,
have graduated open. Be looking at this
and be on the lookout for things you
think are interesting and just always
make sure like you're you're doing your
research or you're seeing who else is in
the coin. You know, don't copy trade
people. Just be like super smart about
what it is you're doing and also uh this
coin just continued to go up a little
bit from where we sold uh which is a
little bit unfortunate, but yeah man, I
mean there's a lot there's a lot going
on right now, you know, and just
a lot of different opportunities within
the market. So, just
look for them. You know, look for them.
Be patient, you know, like there's a a
of different metas that is going on
throughout this year. AI coins,
political coins, creator coins, you
know, Elon Musk tweets, the Ansem coin
obviously has been going super super
crazy.
And so
yeah, the actual skill of meme coins
comes down to like meta recognition and
pattern recognition. Like ask yourself
like, oh, is this coin the first of its
kind? You know?
Is attention growing or has it peaked?
Who's already in this coin? Like those
things are really important, you know,
that's what I'm trying to teach you guys
right right now. And once you're on
FOMO, like it's also really important to
be on Twitter. Like getting on Twitter
and following the top people, you know,
obviously follow me and follow some of
the people I follow and some of the best
traders and whatever. And on FOMO again,
like like I said, like I'm not even
trying to show you this, but like a lot
of these top traders you can just follow
their X directly. Like this guy Juicy
Cooks, I followed him because of his
pianos on FOMO, you know what I'm
saying?
So
it's just important to like really, you
know, understand this. You know, there's
also a lot of traders who are streaming
uh every single day. You know, if you go
over on Twitch and you're over to the
crypto category, like Scented right now
is streaming. And it's important I don't
know why he's streaming Fortnite, but
it's important to um
to go here. God, I love Scented. It's
important to like watch some of these
guys. Like Deku, I was streaming with
Deku earlier today. So
you know, watch these guys. Feel free to
ask them questions. I just want to I
want to ask you something, please don't
copy trade them because like, you know,
a lot of these guys know that they have
viewers and stuff. So like you never
know like who has good intentions or
not. Like simply just learn from these
guys by watching them. Um you know, ask
questions and just have the stream open
in the background because if something
important is happening, like you might
miss it. But like they're more
experienced than you, so they might not
miss it, you know?
And uh did this coin keep pumping? Oh my
god, it's at 38k now. I'm pretty sure
when we bought it
it was at 26k. So I unfortunately just
papered this coin ASMR. I actually would
have made quite a bit of money on it,
like literally 30 40%. Which is uh very
very unfortunate, but whatever, it
happens. Um but yeah, boys, like
watching a good, you know, you know,
watching a good streamer for week like
this will teach you about pace, entries,
taking profits, all that stuff. And just
please understand like I don't want you
to go on here. I think the number one
mistake people do is that they go on
here and they buy a coin. They're just
like desperate to like trade something
and they just [__] end up losing
other money.
And it's just like
it sucks because then they feel like
they got scammed and please understand
there's no such things like insider
groups like I know on TikTok or
Instagram depending on, you know, why
you're watching this video. There's a
lot of people on there who are like,
"Yeah, you know, like insider groups or
all this or all that. Join my like no,
all that stuff is a scam, you know. I
think it is really important to be
trading with people. I always think
that's been super important.
Um
like I had an alpha group called Potion
and you know, I'm still in there and
Pastel and Shocked and like it's really
important to trade with other people. So
like make make friends, meet people,
watch streams, like just don't be
trading alone, you know, it's just going
to help you get a better understanding
of all the different narratives and
stuff like that.
And yeah, I mean yeah, I think that's
fundamental to the most important stuff.
Just follow good people on FOMO, you'll
get notifications, you'll know what's
going on. Look at the feed, you'll see
what everyone's trading, what everyone's
buying, what everyone's rotating from.
Um
and yeah, I mean I I I I feel like
hopefully I went over all the super
basics. Like once you deposit money,
literally just go buy something. So like
I don't know, I'm just going to put like
some money into maybe one of the more
you know, like I don't I don't I don't
even know what I would buy here. Cash
Cat maybe it's decent to buy.
10 these.
Cash Cat's like a really like, you know,
whatever. I'll buy 50 bucks of Cash Cat
on this wallet. If it ever becomes
something, you know, my secret account
is key dizzy pike
on FOMO.
Um and yeah, look all the people that
we've interviewed, you know, this entire
year across the channel have they
they've all said the same thing, you
know, it's like the more time you put
in, the more results you're going to get
out and meme coins isn't like an easy
game. But I think it's very, very
obvious and clear that it's the only
place where people are still
realistically turning $30 into $100,000.
It is 2026 and people are still turning
$30 into $100,000 publicly verifiable on
chain. Like you can literally go to this
guy's profile right now, Samisa BTC, and
you can see July 13th at 4:43, he bought
$30 worth of ponds and now his position
is worth $90,000, okay?
Meme coins is the only place where this
is possible. You can follow him if you
want on FOMO. I have no idea who this
guy is, but I'm saying people have a
platform to really put themselves out
there now and
yeah, I mean, meme coins are obviously
still hot. That is the entire system. I
hope that this very basic guide meant
something to you, maybe taught you
something. Please, again, don't trade
alone, you know, go meet people, go
watch streamers, you know, play small,
give it a few weeks, give yourself time
to actually know everything, you know,
like
let me know what really in-depth stuff
you'd really like to understand about
trading meme coins on chain and
hopefully I can like help you out and
keep making these educational videos. I
do believe that like meme coins are here
to stay forever, you know, like I I
thought meme coins were just getting
started after Trump. That was like a
very big meme and stuff. Um but I mean,
I think they're here to stay. I mean, I
think the ecosystem has absolutely
bottomed. I think in October things are
going to start picking back up and as
Bitcoin everything else starts going
higher, the volume and the attention
meme coin gets also does too. So right
now is the perfect time to start
learning about these things.
I hope you guys enjoyed this video.
Please subscribe, drop a like, uh helps
me out a lot. Feel free to drop a
comment and let's chat. And yeah, boys,
see you guys in the trenches.